<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Performers Archive - Pacific Serenades</title>
	<atom:link href="http://pacser.org/performers/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://pacser.org/performers/</link>
	<description>New chamber music from the west coast</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 10:59:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Luke Santonastaso</title>
		<link>http://pacser.org/performers/luke-santonastaso/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Henderson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pacser.org/?post_type=performer&#038;p=1592</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/luke-santonastaso/">Luke Santonastaso</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/luke-santonastaso/">Luke Santonastaso</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brendan Speltz</title>
		<link>http://pacser.org/performers/brendan-speltz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joseph Maddela]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pacser.org/?post_type=performer&#038;p=679</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Violinist Brendan Speltz is currently a student at the USC Thornton School of Music, working with Margaret Batjer. During the ...</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/brendan-speltz/">Brendan Speltz</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Violinist Brendan Speltz is currently a student at the USC Thornton School of Music, working with Margaret Batjer. During the past several summers, Brendan has studied chamber music extensively with the Colorado Quartet at Soundfest, Cape Cod, with Marion Feldman at the NYU Quartet workshop in New York City, and at the Bowdoin Music Festival in Maine, and the International Academy of Music in St. Petersburg, Russia and Niagara Falls, Canada. He has participated in established professional chamber music series such as the South Bay Chamber Music Society and Pacific Serenades, and has performed several times on the broadcasts from the Los Angeles County Museum of Arts on KMZT. Brendan has also performed in orchestras under the direction of Larry Livingston at the Idyllwild School of Music and was honored to have been selected to play under Helmuth Rilling at the Bach Academy in Stuttgart.</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/brendan-speltz/">Brendan Speltz</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simon Oswell</title>
		<link>http://pacser.org/performers/simon-oswell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joseph Maddela]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pacser.org/?post_type=performer&#038;p=678</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Violist Simon Oswell, who was trained in this country and Australia, has performed extensively as a soloist and chamber musician ...</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/simon-oswell/">Simon Oswell</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Violist Simon Oswell, who was trained in this country and Australia, has performed extensively as a soloist and chamber musician in Australia, Europe, Southeast Asia, and the U.S. For a number of years, Oswell was Principal Violist of the Carmel Bach Festival. Currently residing in Los Angeles, Oswell divides his time between chamber music, solo work, and studio music. He has performed for a number of films, including the Academy Award-winning scores of John Williams (Schindler&#8217;s List) and James Horner (Titanic). He is Principal Violist of the Hollywood Bowl Orchestra and violist in the Capitol Ensemble. In 2003 he performed as guest Principal Violist of the Australian Chamber Orchestra, touring Japan and Europe and in 2004 as soloist on a 12 concert national Australian tour.</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/simon-oswell/">Simon Oswell</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sungil Lee</title>
		<link>http://pacser.org/performers/sungil-lee/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joseph Maddela]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pacser.org/?post_type=performer&#038;p=677</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sungil Lee, first violinist with the American Sinfonietta, graduated from the Juilliard School and received his master&#8217;s degree at the ...</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/sungil-lee/">Sungil Lee</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sungil Lee, first violinist with the American Sinfonietta, graduated from the Juilliard School and received his master&#8217;s degree at the Mannes School of Music in New York. Through the years, he studied with a number of distinguished artists, including Nathan Milstein. He appeared as soloist with the Charlotte Symphony, Grand Rapids Symphony, Rochester Philharmonic Orchestra, Rochester Chamber Orchestra, and the Seoul Philharmonic Orchestra.</p>
<p>A prizewinner at the Paganini International Violin Competition, the Washington International and the Bach International Competitions, Lee was Grand-Prize winner in the Orange County Young Musicians Competition. He also took top honors in the Jukia Klumpkey Scholarship Competition in San Francisco.</p>
<p>Lee has been Artist-in-Residence at the University of North Carolina, Charlotte, and concertmaster of the Charlotte Symphony. His chamber music experience includes playing in the Shadyside Chamber Series (Pittsburgh), the Carnegie Mellon Art Institute Chamber Series, with the Meliora Quartet, and with the Collegium Musicum in Buenos Aires.</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/sungil-lee/">Sungil Lee</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miwako Watanabe</title>
		<link>http://pacser.org/performers/miwako-watanabe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joseph Maddela]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pacser.org/?post_type=performer&#038;p=676</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Miwako Watanabe, violinist, is a graduate of the Toho Conservatory of Music in Tokyo and has won numerous national music ...</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/miwako-watanabe/">Miwako Watanabe</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Miwako Watanabe, violinist, is a graduate of the Toho Conservatory of Music in Tokyo and has won numerous national music awards in Japan. She received a Fulbright grant to study with Ivan Galamian at the Curtis Institute of Music in Philadelphia, then extended her training with Sandor Vegh in Europe where she was active in solo and chamber music performances. Ms. Watanabe was a member of and frequent soloist with the Munich Bach Orchestra under Karl Richter and LACO under Neville Marriner.</p>
<p>Beginning in 1972, she was a member of the Sequoia Quartet, which was a winner of the 1976 Walter Naumburg Chamber Music Award. In 1986 Miwako Watanabe joined cellist Bonnie Hampton and pianist Nathan Schwartz as the new Francesco Trio, which made its debut at Chamber Music West in San Francisco. Appearances included the Gardner Museum in Boston, the Chevron Museum Concerts in San Francisco, the Chamber Music Historic Sites series in LA, and at the Kennedy Center in Washington, D.C. In 1988 the Francesco Trio was the winner of commissioning grants from Chamber Music America and Meet the Composer Reader&#8217;s Digest Commissioning Programs in partnership with the NEA. Ms. Watanabe has also been active in Japan as a member of the Mito Chamber Orchestra and the Saito Kinen Orchestra. In LA she appears regularly as the Concertmaster of the Chamber Orchestra of the South Bay and performs chamber music with Pacific Serenades and on the South Bay Chamber Music series. Her appearances include the Music for Mischa series at the Metropolitan Museum in New York, Martha&#8217;s Vineyard Chamber Music Society, IMA Concerts in Japan, Francesco Trio concerts in San Francisco, and the Naumburg Foundation&#8217;s 75th Anniversary concert at Alice Tully Hall in New York.</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/miwako-watanabe/">Miwako Watanabe</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Roger Wilkie</title>
		<link>http://pacser.org/performers/roger-wilkie/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joseph Maddela]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pacser.org/?post_type=performer&#038;p=675</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Roger Wilkie&#8217;s violin playing has been described as &#8220;having surpassing virtuosity, a thrilling legato tone, and a sense of full ...</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/roger-wilkie/">Roger Wilkie</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Roger Wilkie&#8217;s violin playing has been described as &#8220;having surpassing virtuosity, a thrilling legato tone, and a sense of full emotional engagement&#8221; by the LA Times. Concertmaster of the Long Beach Symphony, Mr. Wilkie has also served in that capacity with LACO, the Los Angeles Music Center Opera Orchestra, and the Real Filharmonia de Galicia (Spain) under Helmuth Rilling. Mr. Wilkie has appeared as soloist with numerous orchestras including the Long Beach Symphony, the Santa Barbara Chamber Orchestra, LACO, and the Carmel Bach Festival Orchestra. He has given solo recitals for the San Luis Obispo Mozart Festival, LACMA/KUSC-FM broadcasts, Swiss National Radio, and is frequently heard on NPR&#8217;s Performance Today.</p>
<p>An extremely active chamber musician, Mr. Wilkie has participated in the Santa Fe, La Jolla, and Mainly Mozart festivals. He has also served as the Principal Violinist of the Camerata Pacifica of Santa Barbara. As a founding member of the Angeles String Quartet (1987-1993) he toured throughout North America, performed in New York&#8217;s 92nd Street Y, and recorded an interactive CD/video disc for the Voyager Company.</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/roger-wilkie/">Roger Wilkie</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Margaret Batjer</title>
		<link>http://pacser.org/performers/margaret-batjer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joseph Maddela]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pacser.org/?post_type=performer&#038;p=674</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Concertmaster of the Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra since 1998, Margaret Batjer made her first solo appearance at the age of ...</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/margaret-batjer/">Margaret Batjer</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Concertmaster of the Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra since 1998, Margaret Batjer made her first solo appearance at the age of fifteen with the Chicago Symphony in Gian Carlo Menotti&#8217;s violin concerto. Since then, she has re-appeared with the Chicago Symphony as well as a succession of other major orchestras including the Philadelphia Orchestra, St. Louis Symphony, Seattle Symphony, the New York String Orchestra, the San Jose Symphony, and the Dallas Symphony. Ms. Batjer has also appeared as a soloist throughout Europe with orchestras including the Chamber Orchestra of Europe, the Prague Chamber Orchestra, the Halle Symphony Orchestra at the Gewandhaus in Leipzig, and the Berlin Symphony Orchestra under the direction of Claus Peter Flor.</p>
<p>Equally respected as a chamber musician, Ms. Batjer has performed regularly at the Marlboro Music Festival and on tour with Music from Marlboro. She has appeared at the Minnesota Orchestra Sommerfest, the La Jolla Summerfest, the Vancouver Chamber Music Festival, and the Naples and Cremona festivals in Italy. Maurizio Pollini invited the Accardo Quartet, of which Ms. Batjer is a member, to perform at the Salzburg Festival in 1995 and 1999, at Carnegie Hall in the spring of 2001, and in Tokyo during the 2002 season. She has recorded the Bach double concerto with Salvatore Accardo and the Chamber Orchestra of Europe for Philips and more recently with Hilary Hahn and LACO, directed by Jeffrey Kahane, for Deutsche Grammophon. She has also made numerous chamber music recordings on the EMI, Nuova Era, BMG, and Dynamic labels.</p>
<p>Ms. Batjer graduated from the Curtis Institute of Music as a student of Ivan Galamian and David Cerone. Throughout her career, she has won numerous prizes, including the G.B. Dealey Award in Dallas. In the spring of 2000, she and Jeffrey Kahane inaugurated LACO&#8217;s chamber music series by performing the complete cycle of Beethoven&#8217;s sonatas for violin and piano at Zipper Hall in Los Angeles. In 2003 they continued their collaboration and performed all of the Brahms sonatas at Zipper Hall.</p>
<p>Ms Batjer has recently been appointed to the faculty of the Thornton Music School at USC as an Assistant Professor.</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/margaret-batjer/">Margaret Batjer</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Connie Kupka</title>
		<link>http://pacser.org/performers/connie-kupka/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joseph Maddela]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pacser.org/?post_type=performer&#038;p=673</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Connie Kupka, violinist, was born and raised in Los Angeles where she studied at UCLA and began her professional career. ...</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/connie-kupka/">Connie Kupka</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Connie Kupka, violinist, was born and raised in Los Angeles where she studied at UCLA and began her professional career. In 1972, she won a scholarship to study chamber music with the Guarneri Quartet and concurrently worked with the violin pedagogue, Broadus Earle. In 1973, she joined the Arriaga Quartet, which won First Prize in the Coleman competition in Pasadena. The following year, Ms. Kupka debuted at Town Hall in New York with the ensemble.</p>
<p>Ms. Kupka has participated in many summer chamber music festivals, including those in Santa Fe, the Grand Canyon, the Oregon Bach Festival, the Mainly Mozart Festival in San Diego, and the Ojai Music Festival. She has served as Principal Violinist for LACO, the Pasadena Symphony, and the Colorado Music Festival, and has appeared as soloist with the South Bay Symphony and Colorado Chamber Orchestra.</p>
<p>Ms. Kupka has been a member of LACO for 14 seasons. She augments her Los Angeles orchestral activities with chamber music performances for such series as the South Bay Chamber Music series and Monday Evening Concerts and is also active in motion picture studio orchestras.</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/connie-kupka/">Connie Kupka</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tereza Stanislav</title>
		<link>http://pacser.org/performers/tereza-stanislav/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joseph Maddela]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pacser.org/?post_type=performer&#038;p=672</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Violinist Tereza Stanislav was appointed Assistant Concertmaster of the Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra in 2003 by Artistic Director Jeffrey Kahane. ...</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/tereza-stanislav/">Tereza Stanislav</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Violinist Tereza Stanislav was appointed Assistant Concertmaster of the Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra in 2003 by Artistic Director Jeffrey Kahane. Dividing her time among solo, orchestral, chamber and recording projects, Tereza has been hailed for her &#8220;expressive beauty and wonderful intensity&#8221; (Robert Mann) and her &#8220;sure technique and musical intelligence&#8221; (Calgary Herald).</p>
<p>An active performer, Tereza has appeared in venues including the Library of Congress, the Kennedy Center, Wigmore Hall, the Ravinia Music Festival and at Carnegie Hall&#8217;s Weill Recital Hall. She has performed in concert with artists including Jean-Yves Thibaudet, Gilbert Kalish, Jon Kimura Parker, Jian Wang and Mark Steinberg. In 2004, Tereza released a CD in collaboration with pianist Hung-Kuan Chen.</p>
<p>In 2009, Tereza was invited to be the Chamber Music Collaborator for Sonata Programs for the Sixth Esther Honens International Piano Competition, as well as the soloist on a Central European tour performing Mozart&#8217;s Fifth Violin Concerto. In addition, she was invited to join the Miró Quartet for their summer program, including performances at Chamber Music Northwest, Santa Fe Music Festival and La Jolla Summerfest.</p>
<p>As a founding member of the Ens? String Quartet, Tereza was awarded the Second Prize of the 2004 Banff International String Quartet Competition, and led the quartet to win the Special Prize awarded for best performance of the &#8220;Piece de Concert&#8221;, commissioned for the competition. The quartet was a winner of the 2003 Concert Artists Guild, Chamber Music Yellow Springs and Fischoff competitions. The Strad magazine cited the quartet for &#8220;&#8230;totally committed, imaginative interpretation that emphasized contrasts of mood, dynamics and articulation.&#8221;</p>
<p>With the Ens?, Tereza is featured on the Naxos recording of the complete Ignaz Pleyel quartets, Op.2. The quartet was highlighted on the Minnesota Public Radio&#8217;s &#8220;St. Paul Sunday&#8221; in 2004, and was appointed to a Lectureship in String Quartet at Rice University&#8217;s Shepherd School of Music in the 2004-2005 academic year.</p>
<p>An advocate for new music, Tereza has worked with composers including Steve Reich, Joan Tower, Toshio Hosokawa and Karim Al-Zand. Premieres include James Matheson&#8217;s Violin Sonata, Bruce Adolphe&#8217;s Oceanophony, the 2009 world premiere of Gernot Wolfgang&#8217;s Rolling Hills and Jagged Ridges and the West Coast premieres of Steve Reich&#8217;s Daniel Variations and Gernot Wolfgang&#8217;s Jazz and Cocktails. She is featured on a new recording of the Wolfgang on Albany Records and the Reich on Nonesuch label.</p>
<p>She is active in the film scoring industry in Los Angeles and in 2009, co-created the new music series, In Frequency.</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/tereza-stanislav/">Tereza Stanislav</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ayke Agus</title>
		<link>http://pacser.org/performers/ayke-agus/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joseph Maddela]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://pacser.org/?post_type=performer&#038;p=671</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ayke Agus is a multi-talented artist: a master violinist and pianist of incomparable skills. Her longtime association with the great violinist ...</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/ayke-agus/">Ayke Agus</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ayke Agus is a multi-talented artist: a master violinist and pianist of incomparable skills. Her longtime association with the great violinist included numerous performances and chamber music concerts with the acclaimed Russian cellist Gregor Piatigorsky in addition to her significant collaboration with Mr.Heifetz on completion of his published transcriptions for violin and piano.</p>
<p>A native of Indonesia, of Chinese, Dutch and Javanese ancestry, Ms. Agus, a child prodigy at the age of seven on both violin and piano, came to the United States to continue her studies in New York. Upon winning several competitions, she became the youngest member of the Buffalo Philharmonic Symphony and was subsequently offered two full scholarships: to Juilliard and to USC. Her acceptance into the Jascha Heifetz Masterclass at USC began a lasting association with the great violinist up to the very end of his illustrious life.</p>
<p>For ten years, Ms. Agus held a prominent position as a member of the piano faculty at USC. Ayke continues to concertize around the world performing in chamber music festivals as soloist and guest artist with internationally acclaimed groups as the Ysaÿe String Quartet of Paris, and the Jacques Thibaud Trio, among others. Her solo appearances with symphony orchestras and solo recitals throughout the US, Europe, and Asia receive rave reviews describing her unique violin/piano artistry as &#8220;&#8230;.brilliant!&#8230;with sensitivity &amp; emotion!&#8221; Ms. Ayke travels across the United States conducting violin/piano workshops and master- classes on &#8220;The Art of Collaboration&#8221; and as lecturer/author of &#8220;Heifetz As I Knew Him&#8221; (Amadeus Press) sharing her lifelong experiences at major universities with teachers and students of all ages.</p>
<p>The post <a href="http://pacser.org/performers/ayke-agus/">Ayke Agus</a> appeared first on <a href="http://pacser.org">Pacific Serenades</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
